<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Naming Things Is Hard</title><link>https://veruu.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Naming Things Is Hard</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://veruu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finding bugs and improving team culture by using emojis as release names 👀</title><link>https://veruu.github.io/posts/release-emojis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veruu.github.io/posts/release-emojis/</guid><description>Our team uses emojis everywhere. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember how it started but we eventually became known for pushing the boundaries and including emojis in emails to kernel developers. One of the activities we really enjoy is naming our releases in JIRA with fitting emojis. Some people recently expressed their opinions that we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be doing it, and it got me thinking. But not thinking about why they are right, the opposite.</description></item><item><title>Simplify your git fork workflow with this easy hack</title><link>https://veruu.github.io/posts/git-fork-hack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://veruu.github.io/posts/git-fork-hack/</guid><description>Okay so the title is a clickbait. This is not a hack, it&amp;rsquo;s just about setting git configuration differently. However, a surprisingly small number of people knows about it, even within ones who consider themselves git experts. If you already know about this setup congratulations, you rock! If not, this is your chance to become one of the lucky ten thousand and make your workflow less painful.
What&amp;rsquo;s the problem? So you decided to contribute to a project that lives on GitHub or GitLab.</description></item></channel></rss>